OGECHI OFFORDILE

Enugu, Nigeria

☑ offorvivian5@gmail.com

) +234 8129444479

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

An office administrator with good project management skills,a good customer service ability, a strong attention to details, excellent communication, and analytical nature person. Achieving a perfect result in any organization by effective management of resources and time, creating solutions to problems and not letting my personal interests conflict with that of the organization.

Core skills

- Positive attitude towards work and learning.
- Ability to work with team.
- Customer Service
- Analytical.
- Competency in English language.
- Attention to Details.
- Microsoft Office Package Proficiency
- Positive attitude towards growth and development.
- Proven experience building excellent client relationships.
- Active Listening.
- Data visualization. .
- Adaptability.

Education and Certifications

06/2018- 06/2021 Higher National Diploma (HND) in Taxation Federal

Polytechnic Nekede, Owerri

05/2015 National Diploma (ND) in Taxation Federal

Polytechnic Nekede, Owerri

Employment History

01/03/24 - till date

Enugu State House of Assembly

Position Held:

Secretary

- 1. Managing Correspondence: handling incoming and outgoing communications, such as emails, letters, and phone calls. ensuring timely responses and proper organization of correspondence.
- 2. Scheduling and Coordination: managing calendars, schedule appointments, and coordinate meetings and events. ensuring that schedules are organized efficiently and that all parties involved are informed.

SWAT continental Services LTD, Enugu Position Held: Accountant

- Developed a budgeting system to monitor spending and ensure compliance with organizational goals.
- Developed and maintained an accurate and up-to-date accounting system that tracked expenses, revenues, and profits.

01/2017 - 12/2017

Umuchinemere pro credit micro-finance bank, Enugu Position Held: Cashier

- Handling customers complain calmly and professionally, resolving customer issues in a timely manner.
- Learnt and followed all stores Policies and procedures, resulting in fewer mistakes and improved customer services.

Internships and other Volunatary Experience (NYSC)

06/2022 - 05/2023

Position Held:

Community primary school, Afaha, Eket, Akwa ibom Class Tutor

• Collaborated with colleagues to develop and implement new approaches to teaching that improved students' performance.

06/2022 - 05/2023 Position Held:

National Drug Law Enforcement Agency (NDLEA), Eket, Akwaibom State Volunteer

- Developed and implemented a successful NDLEA recruitment and registration strategy, resulting in a 95% decrease in drug abuse engagement in Eket.
- Developed a drug abuse sensitization program that increased the knowledge of the bad effects of harmful drug abuse by 95%

Courses and Certifications

01/02/23 - 20/12/23 Google Data Analytics

Coursera

Interests

Traveling, Learning, Reading, Music

References will be available upon request.